<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My music World]]></title>
  <link href="http://ankitsh.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ankitsh.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-06-07T13:25:51+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://ankitsh.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Day]]></title>
    <link href="http://ankitsh.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/creating-a-github-blog-using-octopress/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-02T11:47:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://ankitsh.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/creating-a-github-blog-using-octopress</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Green Day is one of the best punk rock bands ive ever heard. This American Band  consists of three memebers : Billie Joe Armstrong who is singer as well as leading guitarist, Mike Dirnt who is base guitarist &amp; TreCool who is drummer. Indeed, TreCool is considered to be one of the best drummers in the world. Green Day wasnt popular in India in the 90&rsquo;s decade. It gained its popularity from 2004, courtesy to its single &lsquo;Bolulevard Of Broken dreams&rsquo; and since then, its Indian popularity has touched many levels and they are Indian favourites even today.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backstreet Boys]]></title>
    <link href="http://ankitsh.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/some-awesome-title/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-02T11:46:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://ankitsh.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/some-awesome-title</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Backstreet Boys is one of the most popular worldwide bands. It was formed in 1993 but released its first album in 1995 and it from this album only made worldwide impact with the track &lsquo;Quit playing Games&rsquo; from that album. Then the tracks &lsquo;As Long As You Love Me&rsquo;, &lsquo;Everybody&rsquo; form their second album &lsquo;Backstreet&rsquo;s Back&rsquo; in 1997 made them standout throughout the world. This band gained enormous success with its album &lsquo;Millenum&rsquo; in 1999 courtesy to its tracks &lsquo;I Want It That Way&rsquo;, &lsquo;Show Me The meaning Of Being Lonely&rsquo;. They Continued to enthrall the world in 20&rsquo;s decade also with their single &lsquo;Incomplete&rsquo; from 2005 album &lsquo;Never Gone&rsquo; and they continue to do that today also.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Westlife]]></title>
    <link href="http://ankitsh.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/new-post/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-02T11:41:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://ankitsh.github.io/blog/2013/06/02/new-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Westlife is one the best pop bands that ive heard ever. Before its disbanding in 2012, this band captivated the whole world with its melodious music since it released its first album in 1999. It comprised of five memebers : Shane Filan, Mark Feehily, Brian Mcfadden, Nicky Byrne and Kian Egan but Brian Mcfadden left the band in 2003 due to his altercation with his band members. It released its albums in every consecutive year since 1999 except 2008. Some of its tracks like &lsquo;World Of Our Own&rsquo;, &lsquo;My Love&rsquo;, &lsquo;I Lay My Love On You&rsquo; are favourites of many people today also.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
